这题很简单
This is an easy one.
你很喜欢他
You love this guy.
我自己
Me.
不是  他是个不够受人敬仰的天才
Come on. He's an underappreciated genius.
依然觉得是我自己
Still think it's me.
不是你
It's not you.
再想想  有车以他的名字命名
Now think, there's a car named after him.
当然有啦
Of course there is.
迷你"库伯"嘛  因为答案就是我
The Mini Cooper 'cause it's me.
我换个方式说
How about this:
他是降级版的谢尔顿·库伯
he's a poor man's Sheldon Cooper.
特斯拉
Oh, Tesla.
-如何了  -惨啊
- How'd it go? - Oh, not fun.
医生把一个摄像头塞进了我的鼻窦
The doctor shoved a camera up into my sinuses.
我看了
Yeah, I watched.
像《查理与巧克力工厂》里那段吓人的船游
It was like the scary boat tunnel in Willy Wonka.
-查出是什么问题了吗  -有啊
- Did they figure out what's wrong? - Yeah.
是鼻中隔偏曲
It's a deviated septum.
手术矫正很简单
The surgery to correct it is simple.
医生下周给我做
He's gonna do it next week.
你为什么要做手术
Why would you have surgery?
因为我呼吸不顺
Because I can't breathe.
打呼  还会鼻窦发炎
I snore, I get sinus infections...
滚开  这"抢手货"是我的
Yeah, back off, he's all mine.
但这又不是有生命危险的毛病
But you don't have a life-threatening condition.
你为什么要以身犯险做手术呢
Why would you take the risk of surgery?
谢尔顿  这只是常规手术
Sheldon, it's a routine procedure.
我也听你抱怨过他打呼很大声啊
I've heard you complain about his snoring.
是啊  同住的头5 6年是这样
We... Yes, for the first five or six years,
但我都已经慢慢习惯了
but I've gotten used to it.
而且还能助我入眠呢
It helps me sleep.
他就像我的鼻黏液动力助眠仪
He's like my mucus-powered white noise machine.
谢尔顿  我要做这个手术  不用大惊小怪
Sheldon, I'm gonna get the surgery, it's no big deal.
不必多说了
End of story.
行  那我也不多说了
Very well. I'm done talking about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得现在是轮到你猜了吧
I believe it was your turn in the game.
好的
Okay.
我想想
Let's see...
这个人最出名的就是
Oh, this person is most famous
绝不会让鼻子接受非必要手术的残害
for never having gotten his nose mutilated with elective surgery
更不会让自己下半辈子活在
and never living the rest of his life in the shadows
丑陋畸形的妖怪阴影之下
as a hideous, disfigured freak.
你觉得你能给出更好的提示
I think you could give a better clue.
给不出啊
I don't.
我都不知道那是人名  还是打错字
I'm not even sure if that's a person or a typo.
能告诉我为什么吗
Okay, why?
我来听你打呼啊
I'm listening to you snore.
我在想日后听不见了  该如何入眠
I'm wondering how I'll ever sleep without it.
如果能助你入眠
If it helps you sleep,
那你为什么还坐在这里盯着我
then why are you sitting here staring at me
像个白化症版的夜魔鬼
like the albino boogeyman?
莱纳德  羞辱我你忍心吗
Really, Leonard-- insults?
为了等你睡着  我可是在你衣柜里
After I spent two hours in your closet,
蹲点了两个小时呢
waiting for you to fall asleep?
你是在闹哪样
What's your problem?
如果手术成功了  打呼会消失
If the surgery is successful, the snoring is gone.
但如果你手术台上死了
And if you die during surgery...
打呼也会消失
...the snoring is gone.
所以无论如何  你都不会来烦我了
It sounds like either way, I finally get some rest.
莱纳德  我实话告诉你
I have to be honest with you Leonard,
我真的很担心
I'm truly worried.
我跟你说了  没什么好担心的
I-I told you, there's nothing to worry about.
我去查了些资料
Well, I've been doing some research
每70万做全身麻醉的人中
and I've learned that one in 700,000 people
就有1人死亡呢
die from general anesthesia.
兄弟  那你知道这就代表有另外
Buddy, w... Do you realize that that also means
69万9千9百99人没死吗
699,999 people don't die?
你说得也没错
I suppose that's true.
你真是个乐观的人啊
You're such a glass half-full kind of guy.
我会缅怀你的乐观
I'm going to miss that.
我爸妈的结婚40周年纪念日快到了
Oh, so, my, uh, parents' 40th anniversary's coming up
我想不出该送他们什么
and I can't think of a thing to get them.
靠  你能想象
Damn, can you imagine
跟一个人结婚40年之久吗
being married to someone for 40 years?
想象不到了
Not anymore.
所以  有什么礼物推荐吗
Anyway, any ideas on a gift?
他们平常喜欢些什么呢
Well, what are some of the things they like?
他们以前喜欢去听孟买爱乐交响乐团
They used to like going to the Mumbai Symphony,
去年时  我妈觉得他们只是在草草了事
but last year my mom thought they were phoning it in.
我爸说从性生活来看
Then my dad said based on their love life,
我妈的确是很懂"操操了事"
she should know about phoning it in.
-你爸这么跟你妈说话啊  -当时他俩在冷战
- He said that to her? - Well, they weren't speaking at the time,
所以他让下人去跟她说的
so he had a servant say it to her.
或许我能给他俩亲手做个礼物
Oh, maybe I could make a gift for them.
我知道你们俩非常喜欢我给你们做的杯垫
I know how much you guys love the coasters I made for you.
如果离婚了  杯垫归你
They're yours in the divorce.
在研究什么呢
Hey. What're you working on?
还记得我跟你说  如果你去做手术
Remember when I said if you went through with your surgery,
你有70万分之1的几率死亡吗
there was a one-in-700,000 chance of dying?
然后呢
Yeah...?
我研究了数据
Well, I've been crunching the numbers,
目前我已经把你做手术的死亡率
and so far, I've gotten your probability of death
提高到了让菊花一紧的300分之1了
all the way to a sphincter-tightening one in 300.
说得真是时候
Great timing.
我的"检查菊花"灯刚好亮了呢
My "Check sphincter" light just went on.
莱纳德  要是你对外科医生的
Leonard, what if you have an allergic reaction
乳胶手套产生过敏反应怎么办
to the surgeon's latex gloves?
我对乳胶不过敏
I'm not allergic to latex.
那你为什么不戴我给你买的
Well, then why don't you wear the rubber gloves
洗碗用橡胶手套
I bought for you to do the dishes?
跟我不穿围裙不戴发网的理由一样
For the same reason I don't wear the apron or the hair net.
好吧  那癫痫呢
Fine. What about epilepsy?
我也没有癫痫
I don't have epilepsy, either.
你是没有  但手术医生可能有啊
You don't, but the surgeon might, hmm?
只有手术刀稍微拿不稳  你的颈动脉
And your carotid artery is just one shaky scalpel away
就立刻变成迪士尼的跳舞喷泉
from becoming the dancing fountain at Disneyland.
谢尔顿  你知道开车比做手术更危险吗
Sheldon, do you realize that driving is riskier than surgery?
我知道  开车去医院的命丧几率在这呢
I do. I have the drive to the hospital right here.
前提是你能顺利上车
That is if you make it to the car
没有掉下楼梯摔死
without falling down the stairs.
别指望我背[罩]你  我平常够罩着你了
And don't expect me to carry you, I do that enough in life.
伙计  我知道你是担心我
Buddy, I-I get that you're worried about me
我很谢谢你的好意  但我不会死的
and I-I appreciate that, but I'm not going to die.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
我肯定知道我不会死于小行星撞地球
I do know that it won't be from an asteroid strike.
你知道谁还这么说过吗
You know who else said that?
每头自认天下无敌的霸王龙
Every cocky T. Rex currently
早化成石油在你汽车油箱里游泳呢
swimming around in the gas tank of your car.
如果真有小行星撞地球
I-If there was an asteroid strike,
那你不也会死吗
wouldn't you die, too?
那可不好说  我又聪明生命力又强
I don't know-- I'm smart and scrappy,
我觉得我会活下去
I think I'd find a way.
这样吧  离手术还有一周时间
Tell you what-- the surgery's not for a week,
我再好好考虑一下
I'll think about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你考虑的时候不妨想想
And while you're thinking about it,
如果你暴雨季节在尼加拉瓜做手术
if you have the surgery in Nicaragua during monsoon season,
我可以打包票  你必死无疑
I can practically guarantee your death.
是  好的
Yes. Okay.
我明白
I-I understand.
当然  是的
Of course, yes.
我明天打给你
I'll call you tomorrow.
再见
Bye.
我发现伯班克市有一个击剑学校
So I found this fencing school in Burbank
开有绝地武士教学班
that has a Jedi class.
如果你不介意是那个班里唯一的大人
And if you're cool being the only adults there,
那他们很乐意接收你
they said they are.
兄弟  我的父母刚离婚了
Dude, my parents just split up.
什么
What?!
刚才是我爸的电话
Uh, that was my dad on the phone.
他搬出去了
He moved out.
天啊  我很遗憾
Oh, my God, I... I'm sorry.
如果你不想去  我们可以不出去
I mean, if you're not up to it, we don't have to go out,
待在家里也行
we can just hang here.
没关系
No, it's fine.
没什么大不了的
It's not that big a deal.
只要他们开心  我就开心
As long as they're happy, I'm happy.
等我节假日回去看他们时
And when I get to see them for the holidays,
我得过两次印度排灯节
I'll get to celebrate Diwali twice--
一人家里过一次
one at each house.
那就变成了"双"排灯节
That's double the Diwali.
你确定没事吗
You sure you're okay?
没事
I'm okay.
你看起来可不像哦
You don't look okay.
怎么可能会没事  我是一个家庭破碎的小孩
How can I be okay? I come from a broken home.
医生说10点我手术就做完了
The doctor said I should be out of surgery by 10:00.
好的
Okay.
谢尔顿真的会相信
And Sheldon really believes
我们去公共泳池游泳了吗
we're at a public swimming pool?
他肯定会忙着算
He was so busy figuring out
我们泡在含百万分之多少的尿液里
how many parts per million of urine we'd be floating around in,
没空起疑心
he didn't even question it.
百万分之18
18 parts per million.
他仍执意要去
And he's still doing it.
别管他们啦  我很开心能载你去上班
Don't worry about that. I'm happy to take you to work.
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
莱纳德从来不准我在车里吃法式吐司条
And Leonard never lets me have French toast sticks in the car.
我不能有沾上糖浆的手指
I can't have syrupy fingers,
但他却能在马桶里仰泳
but he can do the backstroke in a toilet bowl.
他们锻炼身体也是好事啊
It's nice they're getting exercise.
现在仔细想想
Although now that I think about it,
莱纳德去公共场合游泳时
Leonard would never go swimming in public
一定会穿上他的游泳衣
without his swim shirt.
他肯定带了
I'm sure he brought it.
不可能  去年在魔术山游乐场
No, but last year, at Magic Mountain,
他严重晒伤
he got such a bad sunburn,
得把泳衣剪掉才能脱下来
we had to cut him out of it.
他可能买了新的  快吃你的早餐
He probably got a new one. Finish your breakfast.
瞧  我仪表板上有一整块区域
Look, there's an entire section of my dashboard
没有糖浆哦  快去乱沾
that doesn't have any syrup on it.
你举止好奇怪  怎么了
You're acting odd. Why?
我向来举止古怪  每个人都知道
I'm odd all the time, everyone knows that.
昨晚我还往自己嘴里塞蚕豆
Just last night, I tried to see how many fava beans
试试到底能塞多少颗呢
I could fit in my mouth.
告诉我实话
Tell me the truth.
28颗
28.
-老实点  -其实是56颗啦
- Come on. - Fifty-six.
艾米
Amy!
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
好吧
All right.
别生气哦
Don't get upset, but...
莱纳德得到一个提前做手术的机会
an earlier appointment opened up for Leonard
现在他应该在手术中了吧
and he's getting the surgery right now.
我明白了
I see.
载我去找莱纳德
Take me to Leonard.
你就乖乖上班吧  他会没事的
Just go to work, he'll be fine.
艾米  他是我最好的朋友
Amy, he's my best friend,
就算你不载我去  我也一定会去
and if you don't take me, I'm going there anyway.
好吧
Fine.
你真是位好朋友  这么关心他
It's sweet that you care about him so much.
没错
I do.
万一他有什么不测
And I wouldn't be able to forgive myself,
我一定无法原谅自己
if something happened to him
不能在他床边跟他说  "我就说吧"
and I wasn't at his bedside to say, "I told you so."
你好啊
Hello.
我们游得很开心哦
We had a really nice swim.
省省吧
Oh, stop it.
我猜医疗中心肯定治好
I assume this medical center's already treated
你今天裤子着火屁股被烧伤的地方了吧
the burns on your bottom from the recent pants fire.
因为我是骗子吗
'Cause I'm a liar, liar?
这得由消防队长来判定
That's for the fire marshal to determine.
你非得告诉他吗
You had to tell him?
他死缠烂打
He wore me down.
再加上我意乱情迷
And I was distracted.
他今天用了比较多婴儿爽身粉
He has on extra baby powder today.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
还在做手术
He's still in surgery.
很好
Very well.
他会没事的
He's gonna be all right.
怎么黏糊糊的
That is sticky.
好了  我们聊点手术以外的事情吧
Come on, let's talk about something other than the surgery.
好主意
That's a good idea.
佩妮  你和莱纳德讨论过葬礼的安排吗
Penny, did you and Leonard ever discuss funeral arrangements?
她是说聊点开心的事情
I think she meant something a little happier.
我们是可以当成喜事庆祝一番
I suppose we could try to make it a celebration,
可他是英年早逝
but he died so young.
-有人吗  -好啊
- Knock, knock. Hi. - Hey.
你们怎么来了
What brings you by?
松饼[没什么]的事儿
muffin much.
告诉过你了  不好笑
Told you-- not funny.
他不笑
He's just not laughing
是因为他感觉"难"莓
because he's feeling... blue berry.
好难取悦
Tough crowd.
抱歉  你们真好  谢谢
I'm sorry. This is very sweet. Thanks.
你怎么样了
So, how you doing?
现在没事了  这件事情
Better. I guess the news just
比我想象中给我的打击更大
hit me a lot harder than I expected.
当然
Well, of course.
如果我的父母分手了  我肯定会崩溃
I would be devastated if my parents split up.
为什么  你父亲几乎不和你母亲说话
Why? Your father barely speaks to your mother.
至少他还在我们身边
Well, at least he stuck around,
不像你父亲  一走了之
not like your dad, who just took off.
如你所见  我们是来逗你开心的
As you can see, we're here to cheer you up.
抱歉  拉杰
Sorry, Raj.
你知道你爸妈是怎么回事吗
Do you have any sense of what happened with your folks?
日子一天天过去  他们开始互相怨恨
I think, over time, they started to resent each other,
他们没有好好解决两人之间的矛盾
and instead of talking about the things that bothered them,
反而将其压在心底
they kept it bottled up,
怨恨日渐加深
and the hate just grew.
他们在一起的日子一直不开心  真是太可怜了
It's a shame they spent all that time unhappy.
不过有时候
But sometimes,
你也无能为"松饼"[力]
there's muffin you can do about it.
你懂的  对吧
You get it, right?
你真好  还给他带了礼物
Oh, it's nice you got him that.
这不是给莱纳德的
Oh, this isn't for Leonard, no.
这是艾米买给我的
Amy bought it for me.
进来的时候  他的脚趾头踢到了旋转门
Stubbed his toe on the revolving door on the way in.
你知道那些转来转去的事物会让我头晕
You know those confounded things make me dizzy.
谁让你一直跟着门转
Who told you to keep going around?
大厅里有一株很大的植物
There was a large plant in the lobby.
老让我觉得那是外边
It kept looking like the outside.
听我说  莱纳德出来的时候
Okay, listen, when Leonard comes out,
他肯定会不太好受
he is not gonna feel great,
所以请别让他更难受
so, please don't give him a hard time.
佩妮说得对
Penny has a good point.
他就像在超市里遇到的那个
This is like the man in the supermarket
脖子上有甲状腺肿的人
with the goiter on his neck.
不管你心里怎么想  不要说出来
Whatever you're thinking, just keep it to yourself.
肿得像个葡萄柚
It was like a grapefruit.
人家自己心里知道
And I'm sure he knew that
不需要你拿个葡萄柚去他脖子旁比较
before you held a grapefruit up next to it.
我可不敢保证什么
Well, I'm not making any promises.
莱纳德不仅做了我认为无用的危险之事
Not only did Leonard take what I feel is an unnecessary risk,
他还欺骗了我
he deceived me.
他欺骗你
Okay, the reason he deceived you is
是因为你让人蛋疼
you were being a pain in the ass.
我会这么烦人是因为
The reason I was being a pain in the B is
我担心他  而你们都不担心
because I was worried about him, and no one else was.
不是吧  "蛋"疼你都说不出口
Really? You won't even say "A"?
打死我都不说这词
You bet your sweet B I won't.
我当然关心莱纳德
Obviously, I care about Leonard.
我会和他一起度过余生呢
I'm gonna spend the rest of my life with him.
我就不会吗
And I'm not?
是地震
It's an earthquake.
我就知道
I knew it.
谢尔顿  只是小小的震动
Sheldon, it was just a little tremor.
小小的震动就会把简单的鼻窦手术
A little tremor that turns routine sinus surgery
变成危险的额叶切除手术
into a frontal lobotomy.
我才不管什么地震呢
Oh, I don't care for this at all.
我要去看看他怎么样了
Oh, I need to see he's okay.
谢尔顿  你不能进去
Sheldon, you can't go back there.
来啊  阻止我
Try and stop me!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
为什么不阻止我
Why didn't you stop me?!
我跟你说点事
Can I tell you something?
拉杰父母的事情
This whole thing with Raj's parents
让我有点担心我们
just got me a little worried about us.
你说什么呢  我们很好啊
What are you talking about? We're fine.
拉杰父母会分手有可能是因为拉杰
And Raj's parents probably split up because of Raj.
什么
What?!
人们总说不该怪孩子  但是...
They always say the children aren't to blame, but...
这人啊
Come on.
我不是开玩笑  华仔
I'm not joking, Howie.
你也听到了他说的他父母的事情
You heard what he said about his parents.
都是些小事  积压久了便爆发
It was the little things they kept bottled up.
我可不想我们变成那样
I don't want that to happen to us.
你怎么才肯相信我们不会
How can I convince you it won't?
你对我有什么意见没有说出来的吗
Well, is there anything about me you're keeping inside?
我不会回答的
I'm not answering that.
这是个陷阱
It's a trap.
所以你对我有意见
So there are things you don't like.
我已经踩进陷阱夹里了
And here I am in the trap.
你继续说
You just keep talking.
我要啃断腿来逃生了
I'm gonna chew my leg off.
就告诉我一件你不满意的事
Just tell me one thing that bothers you,
我保证不生气
and I promise I won't get mad.
好吧  事实上
Okay. The truth is...
有时候...你太过...
sometimes... you're too...
美丽
beautiful.
华仔  严肃点
Howie, be serious.
好吧  好吧
dort dort dort Okay, okay.
我实在不喜欢
I really don't like
睡觉时被你的翅膀戳醒
how your wings poke me when we sleep
因为你是坠落凡间的天使
'cause you're an angel.
好吧  也许这个提议不怎么样
Okay, fine, maybe it was a bad idea.
我只是不觉得幸福婚姻的秘诀
I just don't think the secret to a happy marriage
是互相批评对方
is going out of our way to criticize each other.
不过  要加强沟通的方法很多
Although, there are ways to improve our communication.
我曾经在伴侣心理治疗那里学到过...
One thing I learned when I was in couples therapy was...
你和谁一起去的伴侣心理治疗
Who were you in couples therapy with?
这不重要
Not important.
是和你妈吗
Was it your mom?
这不重要
Not important.
所以是和你妈了
It was your mom.
总之  治疗师让我们互相倾诉
Anyway, the therapist had us tell each other
喜欢对方的哪一点
what we loved about one another.
这方法好贴心
Oh, that's so sweet!
我想试试这个
I want to do that.
好啊
All right.
那么...
Okay, um...
我喜欢你能逗我开心
I love that you make me laugh.
谢谢
Thank you.
我喜欢你自强又自立
And I love that you're strong and independent.
但我也喜欢你会帮我撑着门
And yet, I still love when you hold a door for me.
我喜欢我在家里好吃懒做
I love that I'm kind of a slob around here, and...
你却毫不介意
you're okay with that.
呵呵
Uh-huh.
我喜欢我又得工作又得做家务
And I love that I work and do all the cleaning,
你却毫不介意
and you're okay with that.
我还真不介意
See, I am.
这方法好极了对不对
Isn't this great?
快点  笑一个
Come on, smile.
我要用这照片当今年的圣诞卡
This is gonna be my Christmas card.
这都是你的错
You know this is all your fault.
怎么是我的错
How is it my fault?
我告诉你别去做手术了
I told you not to get the surgery.
首先  手术非常成功
Okay, first of all, the surgery was a success,
其次  我根本不想要你去
and secondly, I didn't even want you there.
我不知道哪里更痛
I don't know which hurts worse--
我的鼻子还是我的心
my nose or my heart.
够了  我不想跟你说话了
Well, I'm done speaking to you.
别这样
Don't be like that.
你们俩必须谈清楚
You two need to talk this out.
没错  因为你俩声音太搞笑了
Yeah, 'cause you sound really funny.
谢尔顿  我为没告诉你手术的事道歉
Sheldon, I'm sorry I didn't tell you about the surgery,
但你根本是瞎操心
but you were worried about nothing.
你别以为自己脱离险境了
Oh, you're hardly out of the woods, no.
你还有可能手术感染  出现血栓
You still run the risk of infection, a blood clot,
还有手术疏忽使得蜘蛛爬进
the possibility that an inattentive surgeon
你的鼻子产卵的风险
let a barn spider lay eggs in your nose.
你只要擤出蜘蛛网来  我立马就搬家
The minute you sneeze web, I'm moving out.
我从没想过自己会说这些话
I never thought I'd say these words,
拜托你快来吧  鼻蜘蛛
but come on, nose spider!
别开玩笑了
Who are you kidding?
你多害怕莱纳德会死啊
You were so panicked Leonard was gonna die,
你永远离不开他的
you'll never leave him.
谢尔顿终究会搬出去的
Sheldon will move out eventually.
没错  等他学会如何开门以后
Yeah, once he figures out how to work a door.
我没有害怕  我也不依赖莱纳德
I was not panicked, and I am not overly attached to Leonard.
你担心得不顾自己破相
You were so worried that you smashed your face
都要进来看我
trying to check on me.
你是爱我滴
You love me.
你们说这人是不是脑子被蜘蛛啃了
Yeah. Tell me those aren't the words of a man
才能说出这种话来
with a spider eating its way through his brain.
艾米  你是神经学家
Amy, you're a neuroscientist.
把他的头颅砸开  洒点杀虫剂进去
Crack his skull open, spray some Raid in there.
我喜欢你总喜欢精心打扮
I love that you take pride in your looks,
就算是我早上尿急的时候
even when I have to pee in the morning,
你也能在厕所花费1小时梳头
and you're in there spending an hour on your hair.
我喜欢你太娇贵不肯在厨房水槽尿尿的态度
I love that you're too good to pee in the kitchen sink.
我喜欢你有完全不过脑子
I love that you have the confidence to speak,
就高谈阔论的那种自信
even without giving it an ounce of thought.
我喜欢你头发全都沾在香皂上
And I love how your hair is always on the soap.
搞得我像捏着只仓鼠洗澡一样
It's like washing myself with a hamster.
两位  抱歉我来晚了
Hey, guys. Sorry I am so late.
我刚才跟我妈通电话呢
I was on the phone with my mother.
她怎么样了
Oh, how is she?
还不错
Pretty good.
她买了本《饭·祷·爱》
She bought the book Eat, Pray, Love
然后用它把我爸的奔驰烧了
and used it to set my father's Mercedes on fire.
你们俩在干嘛呢
So, what's up with you guys?
我们在聊喜欢对方的哪些地方
We're just saying all the things we love about each other.
哇  我俩在伴侣心理治疗时也做过
Oh, like you and I did at couples therapy.
你买了什么啊
Ooh, what'd you get?
我在你手术前订的
Oh, I ordered it before your surgery.
是准备安置你的骨灰坛
It's the urn I was going to put you in.
这太变态了
Okay, that's morbid.
把它退回去
Send it back.
这不能退货  我字都刻好了
I can't send it back-- I had it engraved.
"莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德长眠于此
"Here lie the ashes of Leonard Hofstadter.
他自以为是  却不及室友睿智"
He thought he was right, but his roommate knew better."
这个好笑
That's funny.
老天  我会想念这些让人嗨的止痛药
Boy, I'm gonna miss these painkillers.
你干嘛买两个
Hey, why did you get two?
-"我旁边那货是笨蛋"  -那个是我的
- "I'm with stupid." - Oh, that one's mine.